<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: outdoor | KamAcoma]]></title>
  <link href="http://colca.github.com/blog/categories/outdoor/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://colca.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-10T16:36:18-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://colca.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[colca]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[colca7@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outdoor trails]]></title>
    <link href="http://colca.github.com/blog/2013/03/31/outdoor-trails/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-31T20:51:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://colca.github.com/blog/2013/03/31/outdoor-trails</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>2005 – 2011 <br></h2>

<p>Involved in first outdoor activity on 2005, did a lot of 2-days trails in Zhejiang, Jiangxi, Shanxi  and other provinces of China during weekends and holidays, most of the trails are to climb mountains with height between 1400 to 1800m (4600-5900feet). Typical routine is 1 or 2 day camping plus 2 or 3 day hiking.<br></p>

<h2>Oct 2006   Taibai Mountain, Shanxi Province, China (3767m)<br></h2>

<p>4 day hiking with a 30 size team; experienced a diverse environment where middle temperature climate and alpine climate can be found in same area, with glacial remnants from Quaternary Glacier. <br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Taibai">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Taibai</a><br></p>

<h2>Oct 2007  Fairy Lake, Sichuan Province, China (4125m)<br></h2>

<p>4 day hiking in an unexploited scene in Tibetan region of Sichuan province, with 5 teammates; it’s the most beautiful and mysterious alpine lake I’ve visited.
<a href="http://flickrhivemind.net/Tags/jiulong/Interesting">http://flickrhivemind.net/Tags/jiulong/Interesting</a><br></p>

<h2>Oct 2008   Motuo, Tibet, China (1225-4170m)<br></h2>

<p>4 day trekking to the last untouched country in China, with 5 teammates; Motuo is called “hidden lotus” as its mysterious location and isolation with outside world.  You can experience mountains above 4000m, waterfall, the turbulent Brahmaputra River, and sharp altitude falling to 800m in this one trekking trail with endless accompany of thrilling leeches. <br>
<a href="http://www.tibettravel.org/trekking-tibet/trek-to-motuo.html">http://www.tibettravel.org/trekking-tibet/trek-to-motuo.html</a><br></p>

<h2>Oct 2009  Erfeng(peak of the 2nd  sister) Four  Sister Mountain, Sichuan, China(5276m)<br></h2>

<p>2 day trekking and climbing to the second highest mountain of Siguniang Moutain(Four Sister Mountain), we made it to less than 100m to the peak of the mountain due to the big snow. <br>
<a href="http://wikitravel.org/en/Siguniangshan_National_Parks">http://wikitravel.org/en/Siguniangshan_National_Parks</a><br></p>

<h2>Oct 2010   Genie Mountain, Sichuan, China (3700-4150m)<br></h2>

<p>4 day trekking in area of Genie Mountain; enjoyed the beautiful scene of snow mountain, turquoise alpine lakes and time-honored Tibetan temples. <br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grid_Nie_Mountain">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grid_Nie_Mountain</a><br></p>

<h2>Oct 2012   Qizanggou Valley Trail, Sichuan, China (3100-4200m)<br></h2>

<p>4 day trekking and horse trekking trail to unexploited holy Tibetan Mountains and Holy lake deep in the valley where Tibetans pray and do the ceremonies. <br>
<a href="http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.4136213717990.2161159.1062998436&amp;type=3">http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.4136213717990.2161159.1062998436&amp;type=3</a><br></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
